In the last lecture I created a basic react application which you either now downloaded or where you
Na ltima palestra eu criei uma aplicao bsica que voc baixou
followed along,
ou onde
now it's time to install some dependencies,
voc seguiu, agora
for example the react application obviously uses react or react-dom and the react router
hora de instalar algumas dependncias, por exemplo, o aplicativo reage obviamente usa react ou react-dom
so we should install all these production dependencies,
e o roteador reage ento devemos
we do this with npm installed --save, not --save-dev because we want to indicate that
instalar todos essas dependncias de produo, fazemos isso com o npm instalado
these are production dependencies and then it's react react-dom and react-router-dom, like this.
--save, no --save-dev porque queremos indicar que so dependncias de produo e ento ele reage react-dom e react-router-dom, assim.
These three dependencies are all separated with white spaces and are now installed and therefore
Essas trs dependncias so todas separadas por espaos em branco e agora esto instaladas
placed into the node module folder, appropriate entries with the latest versions are also added to the
e, portanto, colocadas na pasta do mdulo do n, entradas apropriadas com as verses mais recentes tambm
package.json file as you can see.
so adicionadas ao pacote. arquivo json como voc pode ver.
With that we installed react,
Com isso ns instalamos o react,
we did install webpack a while ago already,
ns j instalamos o webpack h um tempo, agora
we now need to install a couple of other dependencies to build a workflow and I will add them step by
precisamos instalar algumas outras dependncias para construir um fluxo de trabalho e eu vou adicion-los passo a
step whenever we need them.
passo sempre que precisarmos deles.
So what I want to do is I now want to start with setting up the webpack configuration such that it is
Ento, o que eu quero fazer  agora eu quero comear com a configurao do webpack de forma que ele  capaz
able to handle next generation javascript,
de lidar com a prxima gerao de
css, images and all that fun stuff.
javascript, css, imagens e todas essas coisas divertidas.
Let's start with this in the next lecture.
Vamos comear com isso na prxima aula.